

Aaron **A**ndrews



1+ years of professional experience with the Unity Game Engine 1 year of Full-stack Development creating microservices Looking to make my mark by creating games, software, and tools that customers love using, and that my fellow engineers love working with. Forever a student, I am always looking for new things to learn.

Experience

Unity Programmer,

Sep 2020 - Present

PeekaVR

• Rejoined to create another book

Personal Time for Projects,

Jan 2020 - Sep 2020

Game Library Interface, personal website, and more

Jr Full Stack Developer

July 2019 – January 2020

HCL America (Client, Boeing)

- Full-stack development of web applications and microservices
- Frontend React, Redux, NodeJs, Javascript
- Backend Hibernate, Spring-boot, MySQL, Java
- Cloud technologies
 - Cloud Foundry Certification

Unity Programmer,

Nov 2018 – July 2019

PeekaVR

- Programmed interactions with assets in the scenes
 - o Coding was done with C# inside Visual Studio
- Built out scenes from the books
 - o Unity game engine
 - o Created for VR
 - Used in mobile devices









Unity

C#

ReactJs

NodeJs

Github

Visual Studio

Javascript

SOFT SKILLS

Communication
Customer Service
Teamwork
Organization
Planning
Problem Solving
Presentation

Education

Cloud Foundry Certified Developer

Dec 2019

Linux Foundation

Advanced Diploma of Professional Game Development

May 2018

Academy of Interactive Entertainment, Seattle, WA

Bachelors of Science, Computer Science

August 2016

University of Alaska Fairbanks (UAF), Fairbanks, AK

Projects

Game Library Interface

2018 - 2019

- A game library that mimics the one used inside of the SpringboardVR game launcher.
- Desktop application for a VR Arcade to easily show customers what games are offered.
- Written in C# and powered by the Unity game engine.
- Web application currently being developed
 - o Unity WebGl frontend
 - o Java, Spring backend
 - o Fetches files from a box.com repository

Personal Website: aquinsgreatgames.com

2016 - Present

- Hosted on personal server, running Linux
- Originally written in base Javascript and Html
- Rewritten in ReactJs

Multiple Class and Game Jam Projects

2012 - 2020

- Gleeth God
 - o Unity, C#, AI
- Repair Robot
 - o Unity, C#, UI
- Techno Viking, Final Project at AIE
 - o Unreal Engine, Graphical Effects, Blueprints
- Checkers Neural Network
 - o AI, C++
- Dinaki Adventures
 - o C++, QT